## MERIEME EL GOUSSAIRI

#### **Teacher**

#### **Profile**

Talented software engineer with over 2 years of experience in teaching high school students the basics of software engineering. In search of a position as a Software Engineer where I can express my creative interests along with applying my technical skillset.

#### Education

# Master degree in IT and modeling of complex systems

Sciences and technologies Faculty, SETTAT

#### **Teaching certification**

Regional Center for Education and Training

Professions, CASABLANCA

### Bachelor degree in computer engineering

Sciences and technologies Faculty, SETTAT

#### **Baccalaureate** in physical and chemical sciences

Doukkala heigh school, ELJADIDA

## **Employment**

#### software engineer teacher

Moroccan government, Casablanca

#### **End-of-studies project internship**

OPTech, Casablanca

#### Personal details

#### Adresse

Res al amane gh27 imm216 appt 8 ain sebaa, casablanca

#### Phone

+212 708037661

#### E-mail

Sep 2020 – July 2022

Sep 2020 Mar 2021

Sep 2017 - July 2020

Sep 2016 – July 2017

Sep 2021 – present

Jun 2020 – Mar 2020

Meriemelgoussairi@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/meri eme-el-goussairi-82538215b/

#### Skills

- Teamwork
- Creative thinking
- Analytical thinking
- Java
- Python
- Web programming
- Operating systems software
- Deep learning
- Machine learning
- SQL/PLSQL
- MySQL
- Microsoft Office

## Languages

• English: Intermediate

• French: Intermediate

Arabic : Native